

DILSHAN SANKALPA

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

- https://www.linkedin.com/in/dilshansankalpa-dissanayake/
- dilshansankalpa98@gmail.com
- +94727709787
- https://github.com/dilshanSankalpa
- 902/B,40th division , Dutuwewa,
 Galenbindunuwewe

SKILLS

- Programming Languages
 - JavaScript/Typescript
 - Python
 - Java
 - o R
 - PHP
 - Bash/PS script/Batch Script
 - o C/C++
- Frameworks
 - React.js/Next.js/Angular
 - Node+Express/Fast API/SpringSpring
 - Stackstorm
 - Spring
 - Flutter

About Me

I'm a highly motivated and enthusiastic individual for learning and for personal growth. I love to explore new and innovative ways to solve realworld problems using the language of coding. I am currently holding a computer science bachelor's degree with years of experience in the tech world and pursuing a Master degree program for data analytics. I strongly believe teamwork and collaboration is the best way to achieve every goal.

Work Experience



2022 - Present | Freelance MLE

- Provide creative predictive solutions
- Tech Stack: Tensorlfow, Pycarret, seaborn, weka, orange, Sci-kitLearnig



2023 - Present | Wiley ASE

- Continue the journey of automation
- Tech Stack: Angular, Express, Java, Python, Stackstorm, pentaho, JSM, MySQL, Copilot studio, Splunk



2022 - 2023 | Wiley SE Intern

- Automate internal operations to save time & cost
- Tech Stack: Angular, Express, Java, Python, Stackstorm, pentaho, Servicenow, MySQL

SKILLS

- Machine Learning/ Al
 - Pandas/Numpy
 - Seaborn
 - SKlearn
 - Tensorflow
 - Pycaret
 - Weka
 - Orange
 - Weka/Orange
 - Copilot Studio
 - LangChain
 - HuggingFace
 - Jupyter Notebook
 - Colab
- Database
 - My SQL/Postgre SQL
 - MongoDB
 - Firebase
- Others
 - Linux
 - Power BI
 - Pentaho
 - Docker/Kubernates
 - Trello/JIRA
 - GitHub/GitOrg/GitLab
 - Figma

INTERESTS

- Reading Books
- Listen to good Music
- Traveling
- Machine learning
- Cloud Services

REFERENCE

Dr. Lasanthi De Silva Senior lecturer at UCSC +94773889156 lnc@ucsc.cmb.ac.lk

Mr. Charith Withanarachchi
Associate Software Architecture at Wiley
+94714939387
cwithanach@wiley.com

Education History



Master in Data Analitics

Institution: University of Kelaniya

Class: Reading



Bachelor of Science in Computer Science

Institution: University of colombo School of computing

Class: Second Class Upper Division

Certifications



Supervised Machine Learning: Regression and Classification by DeepLearning.Al, Stanford University



Building Web Applications in PHP by University of Michigan



Mathematics for Machine Learning: Linear Algebra by Imperial College London



Postman Student Expert

Achievements



District 1, GCE A/L, Anuradhapura



The Director's list for maintaining over 3.7 GPA in the first year 1st Semester



Fresh hack - 8th place by UCSC ISACA



Finalist in Codfest by SLIIT



Finalist IEEEXtream 14.0